nimbleschedule.com 2016-04-12

# Privacy - NimbleSchedule

## Information Collection.

Nimble Software Systems, Inc., a Delaware corporation (“NimbleSchedule”, “we” or “us”) is the sole owner of the information collected on http://www.nimbleschedule.com (our “Website”) and from our NimbleSchedule mobile application (our “Mobile App”). NimbleSchedule collects information from our users at several different points on our Website and through our Mobile App.

BY USING NIMBLESCHEDULE’S WEBSITE, MOBILE APP, OR OTHER PRODUCTS OR SERVICES, YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY (THIS “PRIVACY POLICY”) AND YOU EXPRESSLY CONSENT TO THE PROCESSING OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION ACCORDING TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY.

YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION MAY BE PROCESSED BY NIMBLESCHEDULE IN THE COUNTRY WHERE IT WAS COLLECTED AS WELL AS OTHER COUNTRIES (INCLUDING THE UNITED STATES) WHERE LAWS REGARDING PROCESSING OF SUCH INFORMATION MAY BE LESS STRINGENT THAN THE LAWS IN YOUR COUNTRY.

 **Information Use** Information collected is used for purposes including, without limitation, setting up service and conveying information about user accounts and upcoming features and benefits of NimbleSchedule programs. By using NimbleSchedule’s Website, Mobile App, or other products or services, you explicitly consent and agree to the use, sale, transfer, disclosure and exchange of your information as permitted by law and as provided in our Privacy Policy, and you consent and agree that no further prompts to consent are required for such use, sale, transfer, disclosure and exchange.

Although NimbleSchedule currently does not have a parent company, any subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under common control (collectively, “Affiliates”), NimbleSchedule may in the future. NimbleSchedule may share some or all of your personal information with these Affiliates, in which case NimbleSchedule will require its Affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy.

NimbleSchedule will not share your personal information, except in the following situations:

  * If we have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (1) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request, (2) enforce our Terms of Service Agreement or any Licensed Application End User License Agreement, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (3) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (4) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of NimbleSchedule, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.
  * With service providers operating at NimbleSchedule’s request (including, without limitation, payment processors). You hereby fully and completely release, discharge and hold harmless NimbleSchedule, its officers, directors, and affiliates from any claims, causes of action, damages or liability whatsoever related to or arising out of acts or omissions of third parties hired or retained by us.
  * With actual or prospective business partners, which parties shall be subject to a non-disclosure agreement with NimbleSchedule.
  * If we become involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of our assets, we will provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.
  * With other users of NimbleSchedule’s Website, Mobile App, or other products and services under the same underlying subscription or free trial as you ( “Other Users”).

 **Profile** We store information that we collect through cookies, log files and clear gifs to create a profile of our users. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users that details their viewing preferences. Consequently, collected information is tied to the user’s personally identifiable information to provide offers and improve the content of the Website for the user. This profile is used to tailor a user’s visit to our Website, and to direct pertinent marketing promotions to them. We do not share your profile with other third parties, subject to the exceptions set forth above regarding sharing of your personal information in certain circumstances

 **Cookies** A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. We use cookies on our Website.

 **Log Files** Like most standard website servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We use a tracking utility called “Google Analytics” that uses log files to analyze user movement.

 **Special Offers and Updates** We send all new users a welcoming email to verify password and username. Users may, from time to time, receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. However, you may unsubscribe from certain communications by notifying NimbleSchedule that you no longer wish to receive solicitations or information and we will endeavor to remove you from our database where you have the right to request opt-out under this Privacy Policy or applicable law, or where we voluntarily decide to grant the request.

 **Service Announcements** From time to time NimbleSchedule may send out service related announcements to users of the Website or Mobile App. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications.

 **Customer Service** We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account we reply via email or through NimbleSchedule.com.

 **Other Websites** The Website and Mobile App may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that NimbleSchedule is not responsible for the privacy practices of any other website. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our Website or Mobile App and to read the privacy policies of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by the Website or the Mobile App. NimbleSchedule bears no responsibility for the information collected or used by any third party website. As a result, you hereby fully and completely release, discharge and hold harmless NimbleSchedule, its officers, directors and affiliates from any claims, causes of action, damages or liability whatsoever related to or arising out of your access to or use of any third party website.

 **Other Users** As a result of your use of the Website, Mobile App, or other products or services of NimbleSchedule, Other Users (as define above) will have access to information you provide to NimbleSchedule (including, without limitation, matters regarding your work schedule) and may send you messages via email or through the Mobile App. You hereby consent to such disclosure of information to Other Users, and NimbleSchedule shall have no responsibility for any communications from Other Users.

 **Payment Processing** You will be required to provide your financial information to us and/or our payment processor when paying NimbleSchedule for use of the Website, Mobile App, or other products or services. It is your responsibility to ensure the security of your payment details when making purchases through any third party and we recommend that you conduct routine credit bureau checks to protect your identity.

 **Surveys & Contests** From time to time the Website or Mobile App may request information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and address), and demographic information (such as zip code). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information may be used for purposes including, without limitation, monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of the Website or the Mobile App.

 **Chat Rooms, Message Boards, and Public Forums; Third Parties** Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online – for example on message boards, through e-mail, or in chat areas – that information can be collected and used by others. In short, by posting personal information online that is publicly accessible, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. NimbleSchedule assumes no responsibility for messages or other communications you may receive from third parties including, without limitation, Other Users. NIMBLESCHEDULE HAS NO CONTROL OVER THIRD PARTIES NOT AFFILIATED WITH NIMBLESCHEDULE AND HOW THOSE PARTIES MAY COLLECT AND STORE YOUR INFORMATION.

 **Children** The Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act prohibits us from collecting information from any person under the age of thirteen. NimbleSchedule’s products and services, including its Website and Mobile App, are not intended for use by children under the age of thirteen, and to its knowledge NimbleSchedule does not collect, store, use or share information about children under that age. You may under no circumstances use our Website, Mobile App, or other products or services or otherwise communicate with us, submit information to us, or access our products or services if you are under the age of thirteen.

 **Security** NimbleSchedule is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. NimbleSchedule uses a variety of industry-standard security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure.

Even though NimbleSchedule has taken significant steps to ensure that your personal information is not intercepted, accessed, used, or disclosed by unauthorized persons, you should know that NimbleSchedule cannot fully eliminate security risks associated with personal information. You hereby fully and completely release, discharge and hold harmless NimbleSchedule, its officers, directors and affiliates from any claims, causes of action, damages or liability whatsoever related to or arising out of unauthorized third party access to or use of your information, whether the result of hacking, piracy, theft or misappropriation, or any other unauthorized access or acquisition of your information.

 **Editing Personal Information** You may in some cases be able to review and edit the personal information you provide by logging into your account and editing your account information. Although such edits may be reflected immediately after submission, prior information regarding your account may still be stored in a web browser’s cache. You hereby agree that NimbleSchedule shall have no responsibility with respect to retention or maintenance of information in your cache, or in other devices that may be used to store information. In addition, we may, from time to time, retain residual information about you in our backup and/or database, and you hereby agree that NimbleSchedule shall have no responsibility with respect to retention or maintenance of residual information by NimbleSchedule or any third parties.

 **Changes to Privacy Policy** This Privacy Policy is subject to revision, and if NimbleSchedule makes any substantial changes to it, NimbleSchedule will post an alert on this page. If you object to any such changes, you must cease using the Website, Mobile App, and any of NimbleSchedule’s other products and services. Continued use of the Website, Mobile App, or any of NimbleSchedule’s other products or services following notice of any such changes shall indicate your acknowledgement of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes.

 **Contact Information** If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at:

1-866-986-6462   
2588 El Camino Real, Suite F-209   
Carlsbad, CA 92008
